var map_order=["6-4B", "6-4C"];var questions={"6-4B": {"G": {"x": "522", "question": "Name all 3 Great Spears of Japan.", "answer": "Tonbokiri, Otegine, Nihongou", "y": "246"}, "D": {"x": "647", "question": "Name the 4 oodachi swords.", "answer": "Taroutachi, Jiroutachi, Hotarumaru, Ishikimaru", "y": "296"}, "F": {"x": "497", "question": "What does Mitsutada's nickname, 'CCP' stand for?", "answer": "Candle Cutter Pikachu", "y": "306"}, "J": {"x": "307", "question": "What are the swords that are referred to as Ice Cream Milk tea?", "answer": "Ichigo Toushirou, Kosetsu Samonji, Tsurumaru, Uguisumaru", "y": "281"}, "H": {"x": "593", "question": "There are 5 Shinsengumi swords in Tourabu so far. Name all 5.", "answer": "Kashuu, Yamatonokami, Izuminokami, Horikawa, Nagasone", "y": "425"}, "E": {"x": "529", "question": "Mikazuki Munechika is considered the most beautiful sword amongst a group of five famous swords. What are these five swords called, collectively?", "answer": "Tenga Goken", "y": "354"}, "A": {"x": "746", "question": "Name the 5 starter swords.", "answer": "Kashuu Kiyomitsu, Kasen Kanesada, Hachisuka Kotetsu, Yamanbagiri Kunihiro, Yoshiyuki", "y": "450"}, "C": {"x": "745", "question": "Honebami Toshirou and Souza Samonji both burned during a particular incident in 1657. What was this fire called?", "answer": "The Great Fire of Meireki", "y": "327"}, "B": {"x": "809", "question": "Name the swords that the blacksmith will give with a 4:00:00 Timer.", "answer": "Mikazuki Munechika, Kogitsunemaru", "y": "379"}, "K": {"x": "337", "question": "Name all three Kunihiro swords in the game so far.", "answer": "Horikawa, Yamanbagiri, Yamabushi", "y": "225"}, "L": {"x": "349", "question": "What was the name of Nagasone Kotetsu's master, who was beheaded at Itabashi in 1868?", "answer": "Kondou Isami", "y": "174"}, "I": {"x": "427", "question": "What school was Nikkari smithed by?", "answer": "Aoe", "y": "327"}}, "6-4C": {"G": {"x": "522", "question": "Exactly how many beads did you have to collect in order to obtain Sadamune Monoyoshi?", "answer": "40000", "y": "246"}, "D": {"x": "647", "question": "What is the player referred to in Touken Ranbu by the fandom?", "answer": "Saniwa", "y": "296"}, "O": {"x": "131", "question": "Name two swords that share the same seiyuu.", "answer": "Doudanuki and Yamabushi/Tonbokiri, Tsurumaru and Namazuo, Souza and Taroutachi, Atsushi and Imano, Jirou and Iwatooshi,  Aizen and Yagen, Mitsutada and Kousetsu", "y": "254"}, "F": {"x": "497", "question": "Which sword's breaking quote is this? \u201cThere're so many fireflies flying around... they're all so bright\u2026 how beautiful...\u201d", "answer": "Hotarumaru", "y": "306"}, "J": {"x": "307", "question": "What does Kasen Kanesada ask for when he breaks (his breaking quote)?", "answer": "A brush", "y": "281"}, "H": {"x": "593", "question": "Which sword's breaking quote is this? \"What...will I end here...? I wanted...to see a new age... \"", "answer": "Mutsunokami Yoshiyuki", "y": "425"}, "E": {"x": "529", "question": "Which sword was used to take revenge against his thief?", "answer": "Sayo Samonji", "y": "354"}, "Q": {"x": "174", "question": "Who is Nihongou's seiyuu?", "answer": "Tsuda Kenjiro", "y": "206"}, "P": {"x": "52", "question": "NAME ALL 13 MEMBERS OF THE AWATAGUCHI CLAN SO FAR", "answer": "Nakigitsune, Ichigo, Hirano, Atsushi, Goto, Hakata, Midare, Gokotai, Yagen, Maeda, Akita, Namazuo, Honebami", "y": "101"}, "A": {"x": "746", "question": "Who left his mark engraved into Souza Samonji?", "answer": "Nobunaga Oda", "y": "450"}, "S": {"x": "110", "question": "What does Hizamaru's name mean?", "answer": "Knee cutter", "y": "296"}, "C": {"x": "745", "question": "Who is the previous owner of Sadamune Monoyoshi?", "answer": "Tokugawa Ieyasu", "y": "327"}, "B": {"x": "809", "question": "Which sword is fondly referred to as the 'Saint Seiya sword' by the fandom?", "answer": "Hachisuka Kotetsu", "y": "379"}, "N": {"x": "219", "question": "Only three swords in the game so far have used glasses. Name them.", "answer": "Akashi, Yagen, Hakata", "y": "269"}, "K": {"x": "337", "question": "Who is Monoyoshi's seiyuu?", "answer": "Ono Kensho", "y": "225"}, "L": {"x": "349", "question": "Which two swords were obtained from the digging events in the game? ", "answer": "Hakata and Goto", "y": "174"}, "I": {"x": "427", "question": "Which sword's name means \"pressure slash\"?", "answer": "Heshikiri Hasebe", "y": "327"}}};